{
    "id": "8d4dfef20c494feb8b1e1f9d2eadc7cc",
    "title": "Parts Of Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Gokhale was a great Indian ………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "patriot",
                "patriotic",
                "patron"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7f72fdacdc5d4a8b80b1fc1cf1ab6739"
        },
        {
            "question": "From our freedom fighters we can learn many lessons in ………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "patriotic",
                "patriot",
                "patriotism"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "89d28178540945bfb53570d0578942d4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Greece and Rome have a …………….. past.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "glory",
                "glorification",
                "glorious"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "940cdcbbc5a043c4b36ad4fa38532c09"
        },
        {
            "question": "Many athletes are punished for using ……….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "stimulation",
                "stimulating",
                "stimulant"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fd5c314a75594b1e9017f58099839c3f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The patient is under ………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sedative",
                "sedentary",
                "sedation"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5ae7fd7e18c346ae8dc4b096aeeb39ee"
        },
        {
            "question": "For a miser spending his money can be quite ……………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pain",
                "painful"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c298f68577264c4aaea7b42ac6c51bb1"
        },
        {
            "question": "………… goes before a fall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Pride",
                "Proud"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bdd4aeba32c54f12bca28fb8e94192e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The minister’s ………… was accepted by the Governor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "resign",
                "resigned",
                "resignation"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1304313ebb8c405a835272f8256bde57"
        },
        {
            "question": "The chief guest delivered the ……….. address.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "inauguration",
                "inaugural",
                "inaugurative"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "526ea0e60fc54bbd9acbb5eafe67a280"
        },
        {
            "question": "While in England, Gokhale …………. theatres.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "frequent",
                "frequency",
                "frequented"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "133253f2fed647b9a6a3ea8a5159d10b"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………… breeds contempt.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Familiar",
                "Familiarity"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4dd9ea597b0e41e6a968e9db81362aeb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Shivaji was a ………….. leader.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rebel",
                "rebellion",
                "rebellious"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ecaee188cf88405ea1984366b0a22db6"
        }
    ]
}